大家好，欢迎收听今日科技播客。今天是2025-06-24，我为大家带来355条最新科技资讯。
首先，让我们来看看今天的重点新闻。
第1条新闻：Huawei's Self-Developed Cangjie Programming Language to Go Open Source,
Sharing Equal Status with ArkTS in the Future。
据Dev。
to报道，At the Huawei Developer Conference 2025 (HDC 2025) on June 20, 2025, Huawei
officially announced the launch of the HarmonyOS 6 Developer Beta version,。
第2条新闻：Not a wearable, court documents detail OpenAIs plans for its AI hardware
project with Jony Ive。
据9to5Mac报道，As OpenAI fights a trademark lawsuit over its now-scrubbed io brand,
new public court filings are giving us the most detailed glimpse yet into what
Sa。
第3条新闻：Still using npm for everything。Time to level up your JavaScript game.据Dev。
to报道，The JS ecosystem has evolved MASSIVELY。
Here's your 2025 cheat sheet: PACKAGE MANAGERS npm - The reliable classic Comes
with Node.
js (zero setup)  M.
第4条新闻：Harmony-Free: Hengong Preferences - Preferences Settings。据Dev。
to报道，Hello everyone, nice to meet you all。
Today, we are going to talk about the preferences data storage commonly used in
HarmonyOS.
During the developmen.
第5条新闻：Deailing with OAuth SSR in a Next。js project.据Dev。
to报道，Welcome to the CODESESSION001 the first article so far。
In today's article, we will practise end-to-end autherization authentication
system for our b.
接下来是今日科技快讯。
快讯1：Explain in 5 Levels of Difficulty。
快讯2：。NET Learning Notes: How to View Code Coverage in.
NET Projects(with Coverlet  Reportgenerator).
快讯3：Backend Optimizasyonu: Verimlilik Artışı。
以上就是今天的科技资讯播报。感谢大家的收听，我们明天同一时间再见。